Guide to the C. Darwin Stolzenbach papers, 1930-1988 MS2028
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrator, NCTA [National Capital Transportation Agency], 1945-1972; MS2028 Series 1; 20 Linear feet
  - Court Decisions: Yablonski vs. UMWA, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Court Decisions: Zuber vs. Allen, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Legislation: Acquisition of Land in DC for Public Projects, 1965 January (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Legislation: Act Authorizing Closure of Streets for Roadwork, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Legislation: Act 5.6, 1964 June (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Legislation: Act to Establish WMATA Reg. Compact, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Legislation: Act to Provide Transportation Facilities, 1964 July (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Legislation: Act to Vest Control of Street Parking in DC, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Legislation: Advanced Acquisition of Highway Rights-of-Way Study, 1967 July (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Legislation: Agreement, Transit Compact, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Legislation: Aiding in the Development of National Capital Transit, to Create NCTA, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Legislation: Amendment No. 3 to HR 4822, Draft, undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Legislation: Amendments to Senate Bill 326, 1958 February 25 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Legislation: Amendments to Unspecified Bills, undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Legislation: Analysis of HR 4822, Draft, 1965 March (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Legislation: Attachment to Summary Statement, undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Legislation: Authority to Grant Easements for Property of the U.S., other documents, 1962 April (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Legislation: Authority to Locate Vehicular Tunnel under Capitol Grounds, 1964 April (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Legislation: Bill to Authorize NCTA, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Legislation: Bill to Authorize Rapid Transit System, undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Legislation: Bill to Authorize Transit Development Program, Drafts, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Bill to Authorize Transit Development Program, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Bill to Establish the WMATA Reg. Compact, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Bill to Grant Consent to Enter into Transit Compact, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: C&O Canal Report, 1950 August (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Comments by Joint Transportation Comm. on S.1647 and HR 6633 and, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Committee Print, Discussion Guide to Washington Area Metropolitan Problems, 1960 July (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Committee Print, Accelerated DC Highway Program One-Way Street Plan, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Consent Legislation for WMATA Compact, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: DC Area Transportation Compact, 1966 July (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: DC Interstate Highway Projects in the Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1968 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: DC Revenue Act of 1969, 1969 August (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: DC Revenue Bill, HR 11487, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: DC Revenue Bill, Hr 11487, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Department of Transportation, Policy and Procedures Manual, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: District of Columbia Appropriations Bill 1967 09/1966 and others, 1966 September (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: District of Columbia Appropriations, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: District of Columbia Appropriation Bill 1966, 1968 July (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: District of Columbia Appropriations, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: District of Columbia Appropriations, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: District of Columbia, Justifications for Estimates, 1965 September (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: District of Columbia Revenue Bill, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Economic Development in the Washington Metropolitan Area, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Extracts from the House Congressional Record, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Extracts from the House Congressional Record, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Extracts from the Senate Congressional Record, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1972, 1972 July (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Financing Federal Aid and Local Highways for DC, 1964 May (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: "Geometric Design Standards for Interstate Highways,", 1963 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: The Governing of Metropolitan Washington, 1958 December (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Government Agencies Concerned with Land Use, Planning, or Conservation, 1958 December (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Growth and Expansion of the District of Columbia, 1958 December (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Guidelines Relating to the Effects of Highway Projects, 1972 August (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Hearings before Bridge Subcommittee, HR 541, 1945 May (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Hearings before Fiscal Affairs Committee, 1957 April (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Hearings before House Subcommittee on Roads, 1963 June (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Hearings (Congress)-Accelerated D.C. Highway Program and One Way Street Plan, 1962 June (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Hearings (Congress)-Establishment of Parking Facilities in the District of Columbia, 1966 January (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Hearings (Congress)-Transfer of Glover-Archbold Parkway Right-of-Way to National Capital Parks System, 1962 July (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Hearings (Congress)-Transit Program for the National Capital Region, 1963 July (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Hearings (Supplement)-Revenue Aid Highway Program, 1966 March (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Hearings-Washington Metropolitan Area Transportation Problems, 1953 May (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Highway Entrances to Washington, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Highway Extension Act of 1893 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: House of Delegates, Bill to add to Annotated Code of Maryland, 1959 June (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: House of Delegates, Bill to add Sections to Annotated Code of Maryland, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: House of Representatives Report #1962, 1960 June (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: House of Representatives Report #2061-National Capital Transportation Act of 1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 11135, 1960 June (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 9954, 1962 June 22 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 6633, 1963 May 28 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 7195, 1963 July 11 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 10248, 1964 March 04 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 1170, 1964 September 03 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 4822, 1965 February 10 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 7249, 1965 June 25 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 1163, 1966 June (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 15603, 1966 January 09 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 17636, 1966 September (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 17821, 1966 September 19 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 10939, 1967 June 16 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: House Resolution 12708, 1967 August 30 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: Investigation and Survey of Construction of a Subway, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: Interstate System in the District of Columbia, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: The Interstate System in DC, 1968 April 02-04 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: Joint Resolution, Consent to Enter into Compact, 1966 February 22 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: Land Planning Considerations, 1958 December (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Legislation: Land Transfer Act of 1932 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Legislation: The Law of Municipal Corporations, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Legislation: Laws Relating to Washington Transit Planning, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Legislation: assorted documents, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Legislation: assorted documents, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Legislation: assorted documents, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Legislation: Location of Interstate Route 70 South, 1960 June (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Legislation: Location of Bridge between Virginia and DC, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Legislation: Major Highway Problems in DC, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Legislation: Major Highway Problems in DC, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Legislation: Meeting the Problems of Metropolitan Growth, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Legislation: Montgomery County House of Delegates Bill, 1965 February 05 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Montgomery County House of Delegates Bill, 1965 February 26 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: National Capital Transportation Act of 1960, 1960 May (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: National Capital Transportation Act of 1960, 1960 June (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: National Capital Transportation Act of 1960 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: National Capital Transportation Act of 1965, Draft, 1965 April 13 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: National Capital Transportation Act of 1965, Draft, 1965 May 04 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: NCTA Legislation, House Resolutions 6633 and 7249, Senate Resolution 1647, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: NCTA, Proposed Legislation Authorizing Transit Development Program, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: NCTA, Summary Report on Transit Development Program, 1963 March (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: National Capital Transportation Authority, 1959 October (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: A National Program for the Conservation of Historic Sites and Buildings, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: 1965 Cost Estimates for Completion of Interstate and Defense Highway System, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: 1968 Interstate System Cost Estimate, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Nongovernmental Organizations and Metropolitan Affairs, 1959 February (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Organization for Transportation in the National Capital Region, 1960 April (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Parking and Garage Problem, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Planning, Development, Government, and Institutions of the Nation's Capital, 1808-1978 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: Plans and Studies, Washington and Vicinity, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: Preliminary Financial and Organizational Report, 1959 August (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: Presentation to the Secretary of the Treasury, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: Proposed Amendments, Appropriations, 1966 October 05 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: Proposed House Resolution for Department of the Interior Appropriations, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Legislation: Public Law 86-669, 1960 July 14 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Legislation: Public Law 86-794, 1960 September (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Legislation: Public Law 88-157, 1963 October 24 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Legislation: Public Law 88-629, 1964 October (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Legislation: Public Law 89-562, 1966 September 08 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Legislation: Public Law 89-627, 1966 October 04 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Legislation: Public Law 89-670, 1966 October 15 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Legislation: Public Law 89-774, 1966 November 06 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Legislation: Public Law 95-599, 1978 November 06 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Legislation: Public Law 82-592, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Legislation: Public Opinion in DC Regarding New Freeways, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Legislation: Public Participation in Public 12/sions, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Legislation: Rail Rapid Transit for the National Capital Region, 1965 June 21 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Rail Rapid Transit for the National Capital Region, 1965 July (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Rail Rapid Transit for the National Capital Region, 1965 August (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Rail Rapid Transit for the National Capital Region, Draft, 1965 August (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Rail Rapid Transit for the Nation's Capital, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: References to Federal-Aid Highway Legislation in DC Appropriations Bills, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Registration of Historic Landmarks in the District of Columbia, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Reports and Documents, Joint Committee on Washington Metropolitan Problems, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Resolution Adopted by Fairfax County, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Resolution as to the Availability of Public Housing for Low Income Families to be Displaced by Public Works Programs, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Revenue and Highway Program, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: Revenue, Highway Program, and Federal Payment Formula, 1965 May (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Revenue Proposals, 1967 May (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Rock Creek Park, 1955 February (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: "Section-by-Section Summary of the Urban Mass Transportation Act of 1964," (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Senate Bill 326, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Senate Report #1903-Washington Metropolitan Problems, Progress and Prospects, 1960 August (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Senate Report #1906-Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Regulation Compact, 1960 August (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: Senate Report #1157-Increasing DC Tax Revenue and for Other Purposes, 1966 May (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: Senate Resolution S-1117, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Senate Resolution S-3488, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Senate Resolution S-1534, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Senate Resolution S-1379, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Senate Resolution S-2976, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: State of the Union Address, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Statement in Support of Transit Development Program, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Status of Nation's Highways, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Support for Planning in the Washington Metropolitan Area, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Transfer of Glover-Archbold Right-of-Way, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Transit Development Program for the National Capital Region, 1963 July 11 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: Transit Development Program for the National Capital Region, 1963 December (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: "Transportation District Act of 1964", undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Transportation Plan for the National Capital Region, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: "Urban Highways,", 1967 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Urban Mass Transportation Act of 1962, 1962 April (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Urban Mass Transportation Act of 1962, 1962 May (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Washington Metropolitan Area Economic Development, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: Washington Metropolitan Area Selected References, 1949-1958 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Regulation Compact, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: Washington Metropolitan Area Transportation Authority Compact, Draft, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: Washington Metropolitan Area Transportation Authority Compact, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Fallon Hearing, Transcript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Joint Commission to Study Passenger Carrier Facilities and Services in the Washington Metropolitan Area, Minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Joint Commission to Study Passenger Carrier Facilities and Services in the Washington Metropolitan Area, the "Tri-State Commission", undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Joint Transportation Commission-Minutes, 1962 March-1963 October (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Joint Transportation Commission-Minutes, 1962 May-August (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Meeting, Transcript, Transportation Facilities Roundtable, 1960 May (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Metropolitan Committee, Interfederation Council, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade, Metropolitan Planning and Development Council, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: National Capital Regional Planning Council, Interregional Committee Proposal, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: National Capital Regional Planning Council, Meeting, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: National Capital Regional Planning Council, Program, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: National Capital Regional Planning Council, Regional Planning Directors Committee, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: National Capital Regional Planning Council, Rosters, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Regional Planning Council, Meeting, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Commission Meeting, Agenda, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Commission, Organization Meetings, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Washington Metropolitan Regional Conference, Minutes, 1960 June (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Washington Metropolitan Regional Conference, Minutes, 1960 November (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Washington Metropolitan Regional Conference, Steering Committee, Agenda, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Washington Metropolitan Regional Conference, Transportation Committee Report, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Meetings, Minutes, and Agendas: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 12th and G Station-Calculations and Notes, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Beth's Notes from Clarke Clipping File, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Darwin Stolzenbach's 1963 and 1964 Calendars, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Call Slips and Research Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Certificate of Incorporation (of Various Civic Organizations), etc., undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Construction of Highway Systems in DC, assorted documents, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Construction of Highway Systems in DC, assorted documents, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Cutaways of Four Proposed Metro Stations, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - District of Columbia, Department of Highways and Traffic Organizational Charts, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Extracts and Curricula Vitae for Various Individuals, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Finances, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Finances, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Finances, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Finances, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Finances, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Finances, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Finances, miscellaneous, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Harry Weese Conceptual Sketches for Metro, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Metro System-Station Descriptions and Plans, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - NCTA Policy for Final Design, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - NCTA Reconstruction of Rapid Transit System-articls, releases, booklet, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Interstate Highway Sites, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Highway Lobby, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, miscellaneous, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - President's Schedule and Memorandum for Lee White, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Rail Transit Group Conference, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Station Designs, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Subway Construction Estimates, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Three Sisters Bridge, Overhead Drawing, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Washington Regional Planning-Reports, Maps, Articles, 1960-1963 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Washington Regional Planning-Reports, Maps, Articles, 1964-1986 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Documents Related to Maps, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Documents Related to Maps, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1959-1962 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1963 January-October (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1964 January-December (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1965 January-October (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1966 January-November (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1967 January-June (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1968 December-1969 October (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1970 February-November (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1967 February-1971 August (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 1972 January-December (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1973 February-June (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Public Hearings: Memorandum Regarding Hearing on Proposed Highway Route 266, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Public Hearings: Memorandum Regarding PPM 20-8 Public Hearings and Location Approval, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Public Hearings: NCPC, Memoranda of Action Taken, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Public Hearings: NCPC, Memoranda of Action Taken, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Public Hearings: NCPC Transcripts, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Public Hearings: NCPC Transcripts, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Public Hearings: NCPC Transcripts, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Public Hearings: NCPC Transcripts, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Public Hearings: NCPC Transcripts, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Public Hearings: NCPC Transcripts, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Public Hearings: NCPC Transcripts, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Public Hearings: NCPC Transcripts, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Public Hearings: 1961 Hearing on 1-266, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Public Hearings: Official Report, Proposed Highway Improvements, pp. 1-41, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Public Hearings: Official Report, Proposed Highway Improvements, pp. 42-104, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Public Hearings: Official Report, Proposed Highway Improvements, pp. 105-141, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Public Hearings: Official Report, Proposed Highway Improvements, pp. 142-182, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Public Hearings: Official Report, Proposed Highway Improvements, pp. 183-234, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Public Hearings: Official Report, Proposed Highway Improvements, pp. 235-268, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Public Hearings: Public Hearing (NCPC), undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Public Hearings: Proposed 1-266, [folder 1], 1964 November (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Public Hearings: Proposed 1-266, [folder 2], 1964 November (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Public Hearings: Proposed 1-266, [folder 3], 1964 November (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Public Hearings: Proposed 1-266, [folder 4], 1964 November (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Public Hearings: Proposed 1-266, [folder 5], 1964 November (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Public Hearings: Proposed 1-266, [folder 6], 1964 November (Box 23, Folder 15)